National Institute of Labor Education (NILE) Papers 5545
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Tax Exemption (Box 17, Folder 3)
- By Laws and Official Statements (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Project Areas, General (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Projects and Proposals (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Financial Support Letters (Box 17, Folder 7)
- International Affairs (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Education for Democracy (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Labor History (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Residential Study Institutes (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Ethical and Moral Standards (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Membership Participation in Union Affairs (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Aging and Pre-Retirement Education (Box 17, Folder 14)
- NILE (Box 17, Folder 15)
- NILE at the American University (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Correspondence with Larry Rogin (Box 18, Folder 1)
- NILE Films Committee (Box 18, Folder 2)
- NILE Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Youth Employment Project (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Travel and Office Expenses (Box 18, Folder 5)
- School Dropouts among Members of Labor Organizations (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Industrial Mental Health (Box 18, Folder 7-9)
- Automation (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Latin America Trade Unionists (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Labor Interest in Foreign Affairs (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Role of Local Union in Society (Box 18, Folder 13)
- ICA Project, Labor Education in Underdeveloped Countries (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Task Force on Technological Change (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Task Force on Urbanization (Box 18, Folder 16)
- International Trade Union Education Program (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Industrial Union Department (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Press Publications (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Press Releases (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Fund for Adult Education (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Committee on Selection (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Conference on Evaluation Committee (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Fitzgerald (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Public Interest (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Memos and Reports to File on Trips (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Non-Residential Staff Institutes (Box 19, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Union, Staff Training Institute (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Southern Staff Institute, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Southern Staff Finances (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Southern Staff Training Institute (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Conference on Humanities (Box 19, Folder 13)
- NILE Executive Daireetor, Applications, I-faaf.s (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Cooperative Production of Labor Films, Needs and Issues Facing Unions (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Government Contracts (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Subcommittee on Nominations and Structure (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Ford Foundation (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Rockefeller Foundation (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Field Foundation, Inter-Group Relations (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Cooperative Education Program, Labor and Non-Labor (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Human Relations Education within Labor Organization (Box 19, Folder 22)
- NILE Review Committee (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Ethical and Moral Standards (Box 19, Folder 24)
- NILE Problems (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Executive Committee, Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Executive Committee, Minutes (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors, Nominations (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Board of Directors, Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 5-8)
- Board of Directors, Minutes (Box 20, Folder 9)
- NILE Confidential (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Annual Reports (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Steering Committee (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Program Committee (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Correspondence with Executive Director Joseph Mire (Box 20, Folder 14-16)
- Leadership Training for Disadvantaged Unionists (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Conference on Education for Public Responsibility (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Board of Directors Minutes, 1957-1963 (Box 21, Folder All)
  July 1957-October 1963
- Board of Directors Minutes, 1963-1968 (Box 22, Folder All)
  Nov. 1963-Feb. 1968
- Executive Committee Minutes, 1957-1967 (Box 23, Folder All)
  July 1957-1967
- Miscellaneous Reports (Box 24-25, Folder All)
- Financial Documentation- (Box 26-31, Folder All)
- Mental Health Program (Box 32-34, Folder All)
- Youth Employment Program (Box 35-38, Folder All)